어지러운 전국 시대.
The Sengoku era, a turbulent age.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 방방곡곡 접전이 계속되고
Jipangu Country, where the Karakuri people live, is a place of constant conflict.
카라쿠리 무예자들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 떨쳐 일어나고 있었다.
Karakuri Martial Artists take part in these battles, dreaming of victory and honor.
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예자 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
And now, a wild hero has arrived, who wants to be the number one Karakuri Martial Artist!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi enters-dasu!
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden
Musashi Road
(The Story of Karakuri Martial Artist: Road of Musashi)
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
A man always dreams of the day
제일 강해질 날을
when he'll become the world's
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
AH! AH! strongest
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise your spirit's sword high to the wide sky
모험의 길의 막을 연다
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
A skilled Martial Artist wanders Jipangu Country
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
격렬한 칼의 소리가
An intense clash of swords
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Yesterday's battles makes you stronger today
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Art! Dual Blade Musashi
내일은 빛난다
Tomorrow will be glorious
격렬한 칼의 소리가
An intense clash of swords
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Fight your hardest with tranquility
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Art! Dual Blade Musashi
미간이 빛나고 있었다 무사시!!
Shining brow! Musashi!
무사시는 히미코라고 하는 절세의 미녀하고 만나 무예 대회에 출전했다.
Musashi met a rare beauty named Himiko, and participated in a martial arts contest.
그러나 그것은 시라누이 일족이 실력 좋은 부하를 모으기 위해 연 것이었다.
But the purpose of the contest was to gather capable subordinates for Shiranui Clan.
우시와카에게 사실을 들은 무사시는 대회를 엉망진창으로 만들고 만다.
After hearing about the truth from Ushiwaka, Musashi made a mess of the contest.
어!?
침울한 코지로이오
That's Bad!
Depressed Kojiro
계획의 진행 상태는 어떻습니까, 히미코 님.
Ms. Himiko, how is the plan going?
안심하세요, 한조 님. 모든 것이 순조롭게 진행되고 있습니다.
Do not worry, Mr. Hanzo. Everything is going well.
그건 잘 되었군요. 그렇지만 방심하면 안 됩니다.
That is good to know. But do not let your guards down.
센히메 일행 말입니까?
You mean Senhime and others?
걱정하실 필요 없습니다. 이미 자객을 보내 두었습니다.
No need to worry. I already sent an assassin.
역시 히미코 님입니다. 용의주도하시군요.
That's Ms. Himiko I know. How careful of you.
무사시! 이제 간다!
Musashi! We're leaving!
빨리 올라와!
Come here soon!
잠깐 기다리시오! 나 지금 새 기술을 훈련하고 있소!
Just a moment-dasu! I'm now training for a new technique-dasu!
흥, 바다가 적이라면 네 목숨이 몇이고 있어도 부족하다!
Hmph! If your enemy is the sea, then no matter how many lives you have, they won't be enough!
뭣이오?!
What?!
무사시, 네 칼은 짬이 부족하다!
Musashi, your sword lacks distance!
짬이 뭣이오?
What about distance-dasu?
바보 놈. 그런 것도 모르냐! 적과의 거리를 재는 것 말이다!
You idiot! Don't you know that?! You have to measure distance between you and your enemy!
바보는 뭣이오!
What was that idiot for-dasu?!
알겠냐, 봐라!
Look and learn!
흥. 이게 짬이다.
Hmph. This is how distance should be.
흥, 그런 긴 칼이라면 얼마나 멀리 있는 적이라도 쉽게 닿소! 그런 거 하나도 안 잘났소!
Hmph! With a sword that long, no matter how far the enemy is, targeting is easi-dasu! That's not at all great-dasu!
뭣이?! 내 칼을 무시하는 거냐?!
What?! Are you looking down of my sword?!
그럼 어떠오.
Then what-dasu?
용서 못 한다!
Unforgivable!
잠깐! 둘 다 그만둬. 할 거라면 시라누이 일족을 퇴치하고 해!
Stop! Stop it, you two. If you're going to do it, then do it after you have dealt with Shiranui Clan!
그랬습니다. 저희는 중요한 일을 하던 도중이었습니다.
You are right. We were in the middle of an important job.
저런 놈에게 제 검의 대단함을 설명하는 건 소용 없습니다.
It is no use to explain the awesomeness of my sword to a guy like that.
화낸 제가 부끄럽습니다.
I am embarrassed of myself for getting worked up.
기다리시오! 달아나는 건 비겁하오!
Stop right there-dasu! Running away is cowardly-dasu!
작작 좀 해!
KNOW WHEN TO STOP!
네.
Yessir...
무사시, 코지로, 센히메 님이시죠?
Musashi, Kojiro and Senhime, right?
저는 사이고 님의 심부름꾼입니다.
I am a messenger of Mr. Saigo.
사이고 씨가 제게 무슨 일일까요.
What does Mr. Saigo have with us?
예, 사이고 님은 주야장천 시라누이 일족과 싸우고 계시는 세 분의 수고를 덜어드리기 위해 식사를 준비해 기다리고 있습니다.
Mr. Saigo has prepared a meal to thank all your efforts to deal with Shiranui Clan.
어? 식사?! 우와, 가오, 가오, 바로 가오!
What?! Meal?! Yes, we're going-dasu, we're going-dasu, we're going right now-dasu!
임마, 무사시, 흉하다! 대체 네가 먹을 것 이야기만 듣고 눈 색이 바뀌면 제대로 할 줄 아는 게 없다!
Musashi, how unsightly of you! Whenever you hear about food, your eye changes, and you can't do anything right!
응, 응!
Yeah, yeah!
그런 소릴 해도, 기껏 준비해서 기다리시고 계시는데, 거절하면 안 되오!
But still, he went through all the trouble to prepare a meal for us, and we can't refuse that-dasu!
그렇네.
That's right.
꼭 부탁드립니다. 오지 않으시면 제가 야단맞습니다.
Please do so. If you don't, then I'll be scolded.
그럼 말하신 대로 가 볼까!
Then let's go, as he told!
잘 됐소!
Yay-dasu!
사이고
Saigo
여기로.
This way.
이야, 역시 일국의 주인이라더니 대단한 곳에 살고 있소.
An owner of a country sure lives in a great place-dasu!
환영합니다. 무사시, 코지로, 센히메 님.
Welcome, Musashi, Kojiro, and Senhime.
우와, 사이고 씨! 오늘은 잔뜩 먹으러 왔소!
Mr. Saigo! We're here to eat a lot today-dasu!
오늘은 불러 주셔서 깊히 감사드립니다.
Thank you for inviting us to a meal.
아니아니, 계속 시라누이 일족과 싸워 주시는 여러분의 수고를 생각한다면, 이 정도는 아무것도 아닙니다.
No, no, to think about all your hard work of fighting against Shiranui Clan, this is nothing.
그럼 안으로 들어오세요, 오세요!
Please come in, come in!
네이오!
Yes-dasu!
대단하오!
It's awesome-dasu!
사츠마아게 스테이크에 사츠마아게 회, 사츠마아게 샐러드에 사츠마아게 푸딩.
Satsumaage steak, Satsumaage sashimi,
Satsumaage salad, and Satsumaage pudding.
여기에 있는 건 전부 규슈의 명물 사츠마아게로 만들어져 있습니다.
Everything here is made of Satsumaage, the local specialty of Kyushu.
자, 원하는 만큼 드세요.
Please eat as much as you want.
잘 먹겠습니다!
Thank you for the meal!
맛있소!
It's tasty!
그렇게 걸신들린 듯 먹지 마! 꼴불견이야, 정말!
Don't eat so greedily! That is so unsightly!
꺼억
BURP
그런 소릴 들어도, 이것도 저것도 맛있으니 어쩔 수가 없소!
No matter what you say, everything's so tasty and I can't help myself-dasu!
부끄러워서 먹을 생각이 없어진다...
He's embarassing me to the extent that I lost my appetite...
그런 소리 하시지 마시고 자, 둘 다 어서 드세요.
Don't be like that, and please eat, you two.
그런데 시로는 어디 있습니까?
By the way, where is Shiro?
시로?
Shiro?
언제나 데리고 다시니는 개, 시로 말입니다. 모습이 안 보입니다.
The dog you always take along. I can't see him.
아, 시로 말입니까. 음, 시로는 좀 상태가 안 좋아서 개집에서 자게 하고 있습니다.
Oh, you mean that Shiro! Er, Shiro isn't feeling so good, so he's sleeping in his dog house.
그건 안 됐네요. 어디, 제가 상태를 보러 다녀오겠습니다.
That's too bad. Let me go and take a look myself.
아니아니, 그러시면 안 됩니다. 자, 어쨌든 드세요.
No, no, please don't do that. Please eat for now.
왜 그렇게 식사를 서두르시는 것입니까? 저는 단지 모습을 보고 오려는 것입니다.
Why are you so hurrying with the meal? I am just trying to take a look.
그, 그건...
T- that's...
코지로, 그렇게 시시콜콜 캐어물으면 실례야.
Kojiro, asking persistently like that is rude.
우리도 먹자.
Let's eat, too.
저런, 급하게 먹으니까 목에 걸리는 거야!
It got stuck to your throat because you were so hurrying!
아, 아니오. 몸이 저려와서...
No, that isn't it-dasu. My body is getting numb...
무사시!
Musashi!
이 증상은...
This symptom...
역시 독이다. 사이고 씨, 이건 뭡니까!
This is poisonous. Mr. Saigo, what's the meaning of this?!
젠장, 조금만 더 있었으면 셋 다 죽였을 것을.
Damn, you three should already have been dead by now!
식탐부리는 놈 덕분에 밝혀져 버렸구나!
That glutton got everything discovered!
누구냐, 네놈은!
Who are you bastard?!
Kumason
쿠마손
(쿠마: 곰)
(Kuma: bear)
나는 시라누이 일족의 자객, 곰 죽이는 쿠마손이다!
I am an assassin of Shiranui Clan, Kumason for bear-killing!
헤, 이 정도의 함정에 걸리다니 보잘것 없는 놈들이군.
Heh, falling into a trap like this would probably mean you are nothing great.
흥, 함정이라는 건 알고 있었다. 단지 네놈들에 관한 실마리를 원해서 속은 척 했을 뿐이다!
Hmph! I knew this was a trap! I just played along with you because I wanted clues about you bastards!
왜 안 알려줬소...
Why didn't you tell me-dasu?
말해주기 전에 네가 막 쳐먹었잖냐!
You already ate it all before I tell you!
자, 쿠마손! 네놈들의 아지트를 알아야겠다!
Kumason! I will have to know where your hideout is!
꽤 하는 놈이군. 너희들은 빠져 있어라.
I see you're pretty confident. You guys can stay back.
이 놈은 내가 요리해 주겠다.
I'll cook this guy up.
흥, 이 내게 그런 짧은 칼로 대들다니 멍청하긴.
Hmph. Fighting me with such short swords? How foolish.
꽤 하는구나!
You're pretty good!
헤, 내 펀치는 한방으로 곰을 쓰러트리는 위력이 있다. 자, 이번엔 못 피할 테니 각오해라!
Heh, my punch is enough to take a bear down with only one punch! You won't get away this time, so be prepared!
그건 내가 할 말이다! 네 기술은 전부 확인했다! 이번에 내 앞에 왔을 때야말로 네가 쓰러지는 때다!
That's my line! I checked out all your techniques! As soon as you appear in front of me, you're going down!
잡았다!
I got you!
뭐야?!
What?!
좋은 거 알려주지. 난 곰 잡는 쿠마손이라고 불리는데, 또 하나의 이름이 있지.
Let me tell you something. I am known for bear-killing Kumason, but I am known for an another name.
칼 부러뜨리는 쿠마손이라고도 불리지!
I am called sword-breaking Kumason!
내 모노호시자오가!
My Monohoshizao!
그런 느긋한 소리 하고 있을 때가 아니잖아? 이대로라면 코지로가 살해당할 거야!
This is not the time for that! Kojiro's gonna be killed at this rate!
진짜! 중요한 때에는 전혀 도움이 안 된다니까!
Really, you aren't being helpful whenever we need!
해독제 삼키고 어서 건강해져! 이만큼 먹었으면 바로 듣겠지!
Swallow these antidotes and become healthy! You'll become good soon by overdosing!
이랴이랴이랴이랴!
Swallow it! Just swallow it!
이상하오. 몸이 멋대로...
This is not right-dasu. My body is...
됐으니까 어서 가!
Just go already!
예!
Yessir!
에잇, 눈에 거슬리는 놈.
You're an eyesore!
도와주시오!
Help me-dasu!
살려주시오!
Help!
헤, 멍청한 놈.
Heh, that fool.
무사시, 코지로, 이 틈을 타 도망치자!
Musashi! Kojiro! Let's run away using this chance!
코지로!
Kojiro!
내 칼이... 모노호시자오가...
My sword... My Monohoshizao...
뭐 하고 있어, 코지로?! 어서 와!
What are you doing, Kojiro?! Come already!
멈춰라, 이 자식들아!
Stop right there, you bastards!
젠장! 쫒아라! 하나도 못 빠져나가게 해라!
Damn! Get them! Do not let even one get away!
강적 쿠마손을 상대로 무사시 일행에게 승리란 가능한가?
Is it possible for Musashi and others to defeat Kumason, a powerful enemy?
질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
by Subdivers
노려라 지팡구의 별
Become Jipangu's Star
아, 덧없도다.
How fruitless it was.
그 괴롭고 고통수러운 수련의 날들은 무엇이었는가.
What were the painful and tormenting days of training for?
203, 들어와!
203, come in!
어, 나도 들어갈래!
Hey, let me join!
안 돼, 너! 그렇게 발만 질질 끌면 걸려!
You can't! You're gonna trip since you always drag your feet!
가자, 가자!
Let's go, let's go!
아, 기다려!
Hey, wait!
코지로. 너는 지팡구의 빛나는 금성이 되어야 한다.
Kojiro. You have to become the bright Venus of Jipangu.
울지 마라! 꺾이지 마라! 훈련해라!
Don't cry! Don't lose heart! Train!
예!
Yessir!
코지로. 아버지와 같은 훌륭한 무예자가 되세요.
Kojiro, become a splendid martial artist like your father.
미안! 용서해 줘! 제발! 미안해!
Sorry! Please forgive me! Please! I'm sorry!
매일매일 쓰라린 수련의 연속이었다.
Day after day, it was an endless pain.
그리고...
And...
해냈다!
I did it!
그 때부터 제비의 꼬리는 둘로 갈리게 되었다.
Swallows' tails are split ever since then.
음, 고 전해진다.
Well, that's the folklore.
기나긴 쓰라린 시간 동안 함께 지낸 모노호시자오. 어떻게 부러져 버렸는가...
How did my Monohoshizao end up being broken, after being together for all the long and painful time?
코지로도 참, 정말 큰일났어.
Kojiro's feeling so down...
끔찍한 일을 당했소...
That was terrible-dasu...
쿠마손 놈, 이 나를 힘들게 만들었소...
That Kumason bastard made me suffer so much-dasu...
잠깐, 무사시! 애초에 죄다 네 잘못이잖아! 뭐라도 해 봐!
Hey, Musashi! It's all your fault, at the first place! Do something!
어? 왜 내 탓이오?
Huh? Why is this my fault?
무예자 주제에 독 들어간 요리 따위 먹고 마비된 게 잘못된 거야!
Being paralyzed by eating poisonous food is wrong, for a martial artist!
무슨!
No way!
뭔 불만 있냐?!
Any complaints?!
알겠어? 반드시 코지로를 원래대로 돌려 놔.
You will restore Kojiro, or else!
그래도, 어떻게 돌려놓을지 나 전혀 모르겠소!
But I don't know how to restore him at all-dasu!
어라? 코지로가 없소.
Huh? Kojiro isn't there-dasu.
에? 어디 갔소?
Where did he go-dasu?
아! 자살할 생각이야!
Hey! He's going to take suicide!
안돼오!
He can't-dasu!
-코지로!
-Kojiro!
바, 바보같은 짓은 안 되오!
D- don't be a fool-dasu!
이거 놔라. 애도를 잃은 지금의 내게는 더 이상 살아있을 방도가 없다!
Let me go. I do not worth living anymore since I lost my beloved sword!
뭔 소리이오. 칼 따위는 다시 손에 넣으면 되오!
What are you saying-dasu?! You can get an another sword-dasu!
모르는 소리 마라. 그 정도로 긴 칼, 그렇게 쉽게 손에 넣을 수 없는 건 내가 제일 잘 안다!
You don't know a thing! I know the best that it is difficult to obtain a sword that long!
포기하면 안 되오!
You must not give up-dasu!
죽으면 꽃놀이 못하게 되오. 찾으면 분명 찾을 수 있을 것이오!
You can't enjoy flowers if you die-dasu! If we try to find one, then we'll find one-dasu!
무사시... 너 좋은 놈이구나...
Musashi... You are a good guy...
왠지 잘 한 것 같소.
I think that I did a good job-dasu!
어떠냐! 찾았냐!
Report! Did you find them?!
팔방으로 손을 뻗치고 있습니다만 아직입니다.
We're searching everywhere possible, but not yet.
에잇, 어서 찾아내라! 내 손은 그 놈들을 쓰러트리고 싶어 불끈불끈부울끈하고 있단 말이다!
Dammit! Go find them already! My hand is bursting into rage and flaaaaaaaaaring up, wanting to take them down!
그렇겐 긴 칼, 저희에겐 없네요.
We don't have any sword that long.
본 적 없네요...
I never saw one...
아니, 그렇게 긴 걸 찾는 건 무리에요.
Finding one that long is almost impossible.
있을 리가 없지요.
There's no way those would even exist.
있습니다.
We have one.
정말인가?!
Really?!
(남만: 동남아 및 그곳에 식민지를 가진 나라 - 스페인, 포르투갈 등)
(Southern barbarian: SE. Asia, sometimes including Spain and Portugal, for having colonies there)
남만에서 도래한 칼입니다만 이걸로 어떻나요?
It's a sword introduced by Southern barbarians. Would this suit your needs?
음, 별로 믿음직스럽지가 않구나.
Er, it doesn't look so dependable...
그럴 리 없습니다!
No way!
어쩌냐? 이대로는 코지로는 앞으로도 쭉 침울해 있을 거야.
What should we do? Kojiro will be keep feeling down at this rate.
그렇소! 이렇게 된 바 내가 칼을 만들어 주겠소!
That's it! I'll make a sword for him-dasu!
어? 무사시 만들 수 있어?
Really? Can you make one, Musashi?
맡겨 두시오!
Leave it to me-dasu!
여기! 다 됐소!
Here! It's done-dasu!
이게 칼이냐?
Sword, eh?
자, 써 보시오!
Try using it-dasu!
어떻소? 쓴 소감은?
How do you feel-dasu?
응, 꽤 괜찮구나.
Erm, good enough, I guess.
무사시! 칼날이 없잖냐!
Musashi! Blades are missing!
어라? 어디 갔소?
Huh? Where did they go?
칼날이라면 여기 있다!
You can find the blades here!
센짱, 괜찮소?
Sen-chan, are you alright-dasu?!
뭘 만든 거야! 내가 운동 신경이 좋아서, 귀여워서 다행이었던 것을!
What kind of contraption did you make?! Be thankful that I have a good reaction, and I'm cute!
일반인이었다면 죽었다!
An usual person would have already died!
귀, 귀여운 게 뭔 관계이오...
H- how does being cute have something to do with it-dasu?
그만하세요, 센히메 님.
Please stop, Senhime.
무사시도 절 위해 해 준 것입니다.
Musashi did that for me.
둘이서 절 위하는 걸 보고 이 코지로, 눈을 떴습니다.
I finally realized after you two were doing all that for me.
정말?
Really?
예. 지금부터는 칼의 길이에는 연연하지 않습니다.
Yes. I won't be particular about the length of sword from now on.
똥이나 먹어라!
eat shit!
틀렸어. 짬이 닿지 않아...
It's no good. It can't make to the distance...
아, 코지로 놈, 또 침울해졌소.
That Kojiro became down again-dasu...
곤란하네. 어디에 모노호시자오만큼이나 긴 칼 없을까...
This is bad. I wonder if there's a long sword that compares to Monohoshizao...
있소이다.
There exists one.
어, 사이고 씨! 아니, 쿠마손!
Huh?! Mr. Saigo! No, Kumason!
어차피 또 사이고 씨로 변장해 왔겠소! 그렇지만 더는 속지 않소!
You came here disguised as Mr. Saigo again! We won't be fooled again!
어? 뭔 소리요. 나는 시라누이 일족과 싸우고 있는 무사시 군 일행에게 감사의 표시로 식사를 대접하고자 했을 뿐이오.
Hm? What are you talking about-gowasu? I was just offering you a meal, for fighting hard against Shiranui Clan-gowasu.
그런 만큼 명물인 사츠마아게도 잔뜩 사 왔소이다.
And since that, I bought a handful of Satsumaage-gowasu.
뭐?! 아무리 나라고 해도 더는 사츠마아게에는 걸려들지 않소! 사이고 씨, 아니, 쿠마손! 각오하시오!
What?! Even for me, I won't be fooled to Satsumaages again-dasu! Mr. Saigo, prepare yourself-dasu!
체스트!
Chest!
체
CHE
스
S
트
T
이런 큰 목소리를 내는 걸 보니 틀림없이 진짜이오...
Judging by that big voice of yours, you are real one-dasu...
그랬구려.
I see-gowasu.
그래서 날 그 쿠마손이란 놈으로 착각한 것이구려!
So that's why you confused me with that Kumason guy-gowasu!
미안하오.
I'm sorry-dasu!
그래서 사이고 씨, 아까 말한 긴 칼 어디에 있어?
So, Mr. Saigo, where is that long sword you told us about?
아마쿠사 섬에 있소.
It's at Amakusa Island.
아마쿠사 섬?
Amakusa Island?
아마쿠사 섬에는 코지로 님의 칼보다도 긴 전설의 비검이 있는 듯 하오.
It seems that there is a legendary secret sword that is even longer than Mr. Kojiro's sword.
그걸 가져오면 되겠소!
Then we'll go take that-dasu!
아마쿠사 섬에는 못 간다.
I will not let you go to Amakusa Island.
쿠마손!
Kumason!
너희들이 아마쿠사 섬에 가면 귀찮아진다. 이곳에서 죽어줘야겠다!
Things will get complicated if you go to Amakusa Island. You'd better die here!
이번엔 안 지오!
I won't lose this time-dasu!
죽어라!
Die!
아니, 치사하오!
That's cunning-dasu!
죽어라!
Die!
코지로, 정신 차려!
Kojiro, get a grip!
이래선 누가 보디가드인지 모르잖아!
Now we don't know who is whose bodyguard!
체스트!
Chest!
잘들 봤겠지. 지겐류 기합술의 위력을.
I hope all of you saw Jigen Style Shout Technique!
어? 센히메 님!
Huh? Senhime!
다, 다음엔 좀만 더 작은 목소리로 해 줘...
P- please do it with a smaller voice next time...
이제 못 도망간다!
You won't run away this time!
도망갈 뿐만이 아니오!
I don't just run away-dasu!
사리 분별이 안 되는군. 네 칼도 부러뜨려 주겠다!
How guileless of you. Let me break your sword too!
내 칼은 하나뿐만이 아니오!
I have more than one sword!
뭐야?!
What?!
접근전을 안 할 생각이라도 마찬가지다! 이거라도 먹어라!
Even if you're not up for a close combat, there's no difference! Take this instead!
한번 더 먹어라!
Take it once again!
이천일류 섬광검!
Nitenichiryu: Flash Sword!
코지로.
Kojiro.
무서운 시라누이 일족의 자객 쿠마손은 쓰러트렸다.
They managed to take down Kumason, a frightful assassin from Shiranui Clan.
그러나 애도가 부러진 코지로는 아주 침울해지고 말았다.
But having his beloved sword broken, Kojiro was deeply disheartened.
무사시는 이 영원의 라이벌을 재기시켜줄 수 있을까? 그리고 아마쿠사 섬에 숨겨진 비밀이라?
Will Musashi managed to recover Kojiro, his eternal rival? And what is that secret hidden in Amakusa Island?
질풍노도의 다음 이야기를 기다려라!
Wait for the stormy next episode!
허공의 주머니에 달이
Sometimes the moon jumps over
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
the pocket of empty sky
큰 소리로 웃으면
Laugh loudly and
내일에는 아침이 와
morning will come tomorrow
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Don't worry too much about losing
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
Keep going! Go for it!
맨손은 강해
A bare hand is strong
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
That's how life is! Look, a chance
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
follows us wagging its tail!
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
모노호시자오가 부러진 코지로는 완전 침울해졌소.
For having his Monohoshizao broken, Kojiro is really feeling down.
어쩔 수 없이 나는 사이고 씨가 알려준 전설의 비검을 찾기 위해 아마쿠사 섬에!
I had no choice but to go to Amakusa Island that Mr. Saigo told me about, to find the legendary secret sword!
그러나 그 칼은 가질 자격이 있는 자만이 빼들 수 있다고 하오.
But, they say that only the ones who are qualified can pull out the sword-dasu.
과연 코지로의 츠바메가에시는 되살아나는가!
Will Kojiro's Tsubamegaeshi be revived?!
다음 이야기! 지금 되살아나는 전설의 검이오!
Next story! The Reviving Legendary Sword!
질풍노도의 아마쿠사 섬이오!
It's the stormy Amakusa Island!
다음 이야기
지금 되살아나는
전설의 검이오
재미있게 보세요!
Next Story
The Reviving
Legendary Sword
We hope you enjoy!